Washingtoniana Vertical File Index VF.001 VF.001
Test
Washingtoniana Vertical File Index
Undated
Test
VF.001
600 Linear feet
Conditions Governing Access
All subject files will be available by appointment in the Washingtoniana interim location at the Newseum, opening Tuesday, September 19, 2017.
Related Materials
Also see the Artificial Collection for rare historical items that have been removed from the Vertical Files. In addition, vertical files related to Georgetown history are housed in the Peabody Room at the Georgetown Neighborhood Library.
Scope and Contents
Vertical files are news clippings, brochures, pamphlets and other documents placed in folders based on subject headings. Examples of the headings include Residential Sections, Politics and Government, Colleges and Universities, to name a few. As with the book collection, the files cover all subjects related to the District of Columbia: social, economic, cultural, recreational, political, and historical.
- Abandonment of Family SEE Desertion and Non-Support
- Abattoir (Slaughter house)
- ABM SEE Anti-Ballistic Missile System
- Abortion
- Abraham Lincoln Memorial SEE Memorials. Lincoln, Abraham
- Absentee Voting SEE Suffrage. Absentee voting
- Access to Public Library SEE Public Library. Access to Public Library
- Accidents Prevention Bureau SEE Traffic. Accidents Prevention Bureau
- Accidents SEE ALSO Damage Suits; Disasters; Fires; Safety; Subways. Accidents; Traffic. Accidents.
- Accountancy Board
- Acupuncture
- Adams Memorial SEE Memorials. Adams
- Adams Morgan SEE Residential Sections. Adams Morgan
- Administrative Services Department
- Admiral's House SEE Naval Observatory. Admiral's House
- Adopted City. Brasilia
- Adoption SEE Children. Adoption
- Adult Education SEE ALSO Apprenticeship; Public Schools. Americanization; Public Schools. Night; Settlements; Vocational Education.
- Advertising SEE ALSO Billboards
- Advertising agencies SEE Business, Individual. Advertising agencies
- Advisory Neighborhood Commissions SEE Politics and Government. Advisory Neighborhood Commissions (ANCs)
- Aeronautics SEE ALSO Airports; Presidential Airplanes and Helicopters
- Aeronautics. Accidents
- Aeronautics. Commercial Flights (includes air mail)
- Aeronautics. Courses and Schools
- Aeronautics. Demonstrations and Races
- Aeronautics. Helicopters SEE ALSO Police. Helicopters
- Aeronautics. Model Airplanes
- Affirmative Action SEE Employment Services, D.C. Department of; Manpower, D.C. Department of
- AFL-CIO Building 1955 [American Federation of Labor/Congress of Industrial Organizations] SEE American Federation of Labor Building
- African Art SEE Museums. Museum of African Art; Smithsonian Institution. African Art Museum
- African Art Museum SEE Smithsonian Institution. African Art Museum
- Afro-American Newspapers SEE Newspapers. Afro-American
- Afro-Centric Courses of Study SEE Public Schools. Courses of Study. Afro-Centric Curriculum.
- Aged SEE Old Age
- Aging, Commission on
- Agriculture, U.S. Department of. Building
- Agriculture, U.S. Department of. School
- Aid to Families with Dependent Children (AFDC) SEE Public Welfare
- AIDS/HIV SEE Diseases. AIDS/HIV
- Air and Space Museum SEE Smithsonian Institution. Air and Space Museum
- Air Conditioning SEE ALSO Capitol. Air Conditioning; Refrigeration and Air Conditioning Board
- Air Mail SEE Aeronautics. Commercial Flights
- Air Pollution SEE ALSO Heat and Power Plants; Refuse and Refuse Disposal
- Air Raid Precautions SEE Defense. Air Raid Precautions
- Air Transportation SEE Business, Individual. Air transportation
- Airplanes SEE Aeronautics
- Airport design SEE Business, Individual. Airport design
- Airports (by date)
- Airports. A-Z
- Airports. Andrews Field
- Airports. Baltimore Washington International
- Airports. Bolling Field
- Airports. Burke, Va. Rejected site
- Airports. Dulles International
- Airports. Legislation
- Airports. Metropolitan Washington Airport Authority
- Airports. Municipal
- Airports. National
- Airports. Ronald Reagan National
- Airports. Washington Hoover
- Airspace
- Alcohol Beverage Control Board SEE Liquor. Alcoholic Beverage Control Board
- Alcohol Treatment Centers SEE Alcoholism; Liquor. Alcoholic clinic
- Alcoholism SEE ALSO Liquor. Alcoholics; Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Alcoholics Anonymous
- Aldermen, Board of SEE Politics and government. Aldermen, Board of
- Alexandria. (By date)
- Alexandria. House Tours
- Alexandria. Houses
- Alexandria. Houses - Carlyle House
- Alexandria. Landmarks - A-Z
- Alexandria. Landmarks - Gatsby Tavern
- Alexandria. Landmarks - Masonic Memorial
- Alexandria. Pamphlets
- Alexandria and Washington Street Railway SEE Street Railways. Alexandria and Washington
- Aliens SEE Ethnic Groups
- Alley Dwelling Authority SEE Housing. Alley Dwelling Authority
- Alleys (by date) SEE ALSO Housing. Alley Dwelling Authority; Slums
- Alleys. A-Z
- Alleys. Blagden
- Alleys. Dixon Court
- Alleys. Legislation
- Alleys. London Court
- Alleys. Louse Alley
- Alleys. Movement to Abolish SEE Alleys. Legislation; Housing. Alley Dwelling Authority
- Alleys. Schott's
- Alleys. Snow's Court
- Alleys. Temperance Court
- Alleys. Terrace Court
- Alleys. Willow Tree
- Alms House SEE ALSO Old Age. Old Age Homes
- Alterations (clothing) SEE Business, Individual. Alterations (clothing)
- Alternative Media SEE Newspapers. Alternative Media
- Altitude SEE Topography
- Ambulances SEE ALSO Emergency Medical services
- Amendment 23 SEE Suffrage. National Representation.
- American Beauty Rose SEE Flowers. Official (American Beauty Rose)
- American Federation of Labor Building
- American Film Institute SEE John F. Kennedy Center. American Film Institute; Theaters. American Film Institute (AFI)
- American Immigration Law Center
- American Institute of Architects Building SEE Houses. General. Octagon Houses
- American National Red Cross Building SEE ALSO Red Cross
- American Pharmaceutical Association Building SEE Buildings. Office. Constitution Ave. NW. American Pharmaceutical Association
- American Theater SEE Theaters. American
- American University SEE Colleges and Universities. American University
- Americanization School SEE Public Schools. Americanization
- AMTRAK SEE Railroads. AMTRAK
- Anacostia and Potomac River Street Railway SEE Street Railways. Anacostia and Potomac River
- Anacostia Naval Station SEE Naval Station. Anacostia
- Anacostia Community Public School SEE Public Schools. Community. Anacostia
- Anacostia Park SEE Parks. Anacostia
- Anacostia River and Flats (by date) SEE ALSO Parks. Anacostia
- Anacostia River and Flats. Legislation SEE ALSO Parks. Anacostia
- Analostan Island SEE Theodore Roosevelt Island
- Anatomical Board
- Andrew Jackson Memorial SEE Memorials. Jackson, Andrew
- Animal Cruelty SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Animal Cruelty
- Animal Production SEE Business, Individual. Animals Production (fur bearing)
- Animals (by date) SEE ALSO Cats and Cat Shows; Dogs; Farms and Farming; Fauna and Flora; Snakes and Reptiles
- Animals. Animal Rights
- Animals. Prehistoric SEE Fauna and Flora
- Anne B. Hohenning SEE Settlements. Anne B. Hohenning
- Antennas and Satellites
- Anthrax SEE Terrorism. Anthrax
- Anti-Ballistic Missile System
- Anti-crime programs SEE Crime and Criminals. Anti-crime programs
- Anti-Nuclear Movement
- Anti-Poverty March
- Anti-Poverty Programs. A-Z
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Appropriations
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Change
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Community Development Services
- Anti-Poverty Programs. D.C. Public Library
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Education
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Job Corps
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Neighborhood Youth Corps
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Office of Economic Opportunity. DC Public Information Center
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Opportunities Industrialization Centers (OIC)
- Anti-Poverty Programs. Peoples Involvement Corporation (PIC)
- Anti-Poverty Programs. United Planning Organization (UPO)
- Anti-Poverty Programs Booklets
- Antioch School of Law SEE Colleges and Universities. Antioch School of Law
- Antiques SEE ALSO Business, Individual. Antiques, retail.
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives (by date) SEE ALSO Condominiums
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives A-Z SEE ALSO Condominiums
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Belmont Park
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Cairo
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Cambridge
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Canterbury House
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Capitol Hill Lodge
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Capitol Park
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Carlyn Apartments
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Carrolsburg Square
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Carthage
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Cathedral
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Cathedral Mansions
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Cathedral Park
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Cathedral West
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Chatsworth
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Clifton Terrace
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Colonnade
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Dupont Circle
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. The Hastings
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Jocelyn
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Kennedy-Warren
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Paradise at Parkside
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Potomac Gardens
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Regency House
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Sixteenth Street
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Van Ness
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Watergate
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Westchester
- Apartment Houses, Condominiums, Cooperatives. Westmoreland
- Apex Building SEE Federal Trade Commission Building
- Aphasic Children SEE Private Schools. School for Aphasic Children
- Appeals and Review, Board of
- Appliances SEE Business, Individual. Electronic appliances
- Appraisers SEE Business, Individual. Appraisers
- Apprenticeship
- Appropriations SEE Finances. Appropriations
- Aquariums
- Aquariums - Commerce Department
- Aquatic Gardens SEE ALSO Kenilworth Aquatic Gardens
- Aqueduct, Washington SEE ALSO Bridges, Cabin John; Reservoirs; Streets. McArthur Blvd.; Water Supply
- Aqueduct, Washington. Pamphlets
- Arab Information Center
- Arboretum SEE ALSO Botanic Garden, U.S.
- Arcade SEE Markets. Arcade
- Archaeology
- Archery SEE Sports. Archery
- Architect of the Capitol SEE Capitol. Architect
- Architects, Board of Examiners and Registrars of
- Architecture (by date)
- Archives, D.C.
- Area Labor Summary SEE Statistics. Area Labor Summary
- Area of D.C. (69 sq. mi.) SEE Topography
- Arena Stage SEE Theaters. Arena Stage
- Arlington Cantonment. SEE Arlington County, A-Z. Arlington Cantonment
- Arlington Cemetery (by date)
- Arlington Cemetery. John F. Kennedy
- Arlington Cemetery. Legislation
- Arlington Cemetery. Robert F. Kennedy
- Arlington County (by date)
- Arlington County. A-Z. Arlington Cantonment
- Arlington County. A-Z. Pamphlets
- Arlington County. A-Z. Retrocession SEE ALSO Retrocession; Retrocession. Maryland
- Arlington County. A-Z. Transportation
- Arlington Mansion
- Arlington National Cemetery SEE Arlington Cemetery
- Armed Forces Day SEE Days, Special. Armed Forces Day
- Armed Forces Institute of Pathology SEE Hospitals. Walter Reed
- Armed Forces Library SEE Libraries. U.S. Armed Forces Medical Library
- Armed Forces Museum SEE Museums. Armed Forces; Temple of Understanding (Proposed)
- Armistice Day SEE Days, Special. Armistice Day
- Armored Car Service SEE Business, Individual. Armored Car Service
- Armory (by date)
- Armory. Sixth (6th) Marines
- Army Air Force Band SEE Music. Bands. Army Air Force Band
- Army and Air Force Building SEE Forestall Building
- Army Canine Corps SEE Dogs. Army Canine Corps
- Army Map Service SEE Dalecarlia Parkway
- Army Medical Center SEE Hospitals. Walter Reed
- Army Medical Fountain SEE Fountains. Army Medical Fountain
- Army War College SEE ALSO Arsenal; Fort Leslie McNair; National War College
- Arsenal (1803-1881) Greenleaf Point SEE ALSO Army War College, 1903-1946; Fort Leslie McNair
- Arson SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Arson
- Art
- Art (pamphlets)
- Art, A-Z. Courses and Schools
- Art, A-Z. Courses and Schools. Abbott School of Fine and Commercial Art
- Art, A-Z. Courses and Schools. National Art School/ National School of Fine and Applied Arts
- Art, A-Z. Exhibitions and Organizations SEE ALSO Exhibitions
- Art, A-Z. Exhibitions and Organizations. Pamphlets
- Art, A-Z. Exhibitions and Organizations. Washington Watercolor Association
- Art. Public Art
- Art. Washington Project for the Arts
- Art Consultants SEE Business, Individual. Art Consultants
- Art Galleries (by date)
- Art Galleries, A-Z
- Art Galleries. Franz Bader Gallery
- Art Galleries. Barnett Aden Gallery
- Art Galleries. Corcoran Gallery of Art (by date)
- Art Galleries. Corcoran Gallery of Art. Biennial Exhibitions
- Art Galleries. Corcoran Gallery of Art. Clark Collection
- Art Galleries. Corcoran Gallery of Art. Pamphlets
- Art Galleries. Corcoran Gallery of Art. School
- Art Galleries. Corcoran Gallery of Art. Washington Area Exhibit
- Art Galleries. Freer Gallery of Art SEE Smithsonian Institution. Freer Gallery of Art.
- Art Galleries. Hirshhorn Museum SEE Smithsonian Institution. Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden
- Art Galleries. Institute of Contemporary Art
- Art Galleries. Kreeger Museum SEE ALSO Houses. 2401 Foxhall Road NW. Kreeger
- Art Galleries. Museum of Modern Art
- Art Galleries. National Collection of Fine Arts SEE Smithsonian Institution. National Collection of Fine Arts
- Art Galleries. National Gallery of Art
- Art Galleries. National Gallery of Art. East Wing
- Art Galleries. National Gallery of Art. Music Programs
- Art Galleries. National Gallery of Art. Pamphlets
- Art Galleries. National Gallery of Caricature and Cartoon Art
- Art Galleries. National Geographic Society's Explorer Hall
- Art Galleries. National Museum of Women in the Arts
- Art Galleries. National Portrait Gallery SEE Smithsonian Institution. National Portrait Gallery
- Art Galleries. Phillips Memorial Art Gallery SEE ALSO Private Schools. Phillips Gallery Art School; Private Schools. Studio House
- Art Galleries. Renwick Gallery SEE Smithsonian Institution. Renwick Gallery
- Art Galleries. Arthur M. Sackler Gallery. SEE Smithsonian Institutions. Arthur M. Sackler Gallery
- Art Galleries. Very Special Arts Gallery
- Art Galleries. Washington Gallery of Modern Art
- Art Galleries. Washington Women's Art Center
- Art Galleries. Whyte Bookshop Gallery
- Art Galleries. Works Progress Administration
- Art Schools SEE Private Schools. Specific name of school
- Artificial Limbs SEE Businesses, Individual. Artificial Limbs
- Arts and Humanities Commission, D.C.
- Asbestos
- Asian and Pacific Islander Affairs, D.C. Commission on
- Aspen Hill Pet Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. Aspen Hill (pets)
- Asphalt Plant
- Assault SEE Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Assault
- Assessor's Office
- Associations; Civic Organizations SEE Societies, Clubs and Organizations
- Astrology
- Astronomy
- Athletics SEE Sports; Public Schools. Sports
- Atomic Bomb-Proof Buildings
- Atomic Energy
- Atomic Energy Commission Building SEE Public Health Services Building
- Atomic Research Lab (proposed)
- Auction Rooms and Auctioneers SEE Business, Individual. Auction Rooms and Auctioneers
- Auctions
- Audio-Visual Material
- Audit
- Auditoriums
- Auditoriums. Washington Auditorium
- Auditor's Office SEE ALSO Internal Audit Office
- Authors. Washington SEE Literary Washington
- Automatic food machines SEE Business, Individual. Automatic food machines
- Automation
- Automobile agents (dealers) SEE Business, Individual. Automobile agents (dealers)
- Automobile dealers, used SEE Business, Individual. Automobile dealers, used
- Automobile drivers
- Automobile driving instruction SEE Business, Individual. Automobile driving instruction
- Automobile Racing SEE Sports. Automobile Racing
- Automobile rental SEE Business, Individual. Automobile rental
- Automobiles SEE ALSO Traffic; Transportation
- Automobiles. Carpools
- Automobiles. Drivers' Permit
- Automobiles. Driver's Test for Drunkenness
- Automobiles. Driving While Intoxicated SEE ALSO Crimes and Criminals. Specific Cases. DUI
- Automobiles. Firms
- Automobiles. Gasoline SEE ALSO Taxation. Gasoline
- Automobiles. Inspection
- Automobiles. Insurance
- Automobiles. Insurance. Legislation
- Automobiles. Legislation
- Automobiles. Official
- Automobiles. Pollution
- Automobiles. Reciprocity
- Automobiles. Registration
- Automobiles. Safety
- Automobiles. Service
- Automobiles. Sharing
- Automobiles. Shows
- Automobiles. Statistics
- Automobiles. Tags
- Automobiles. Taxes SEE Taxation. Automobile
- Automobiles. Theft
- Automobiles. Tire Rationing SEE World War II. Rationing
- Automobiles. Tires
- Automobiles. Titles
- Automobiles. Traffic SEE Traffic
- Auxiliary Police Force SEE Police. Auxiliary Force
- Aviation SEE Aeronautics
- Awards SEE ALSO Theaters. Awards. Helen Hayes
- Awards and Scholarships SEE Public Schools. Awards and Scholarships
- Awning manufacturers SEE Business, Individual. Awning manufacturers
- Ayre and Taylor SEE Stores. Ayre and Taylor
- Baby sitters SEE Business, Individual. Babysitters
- Bail Reform Acts of 1966 and 1969 SEE Courts. Legislation. Bail Reform Acts of 1966 and 1969
- Bakeries SEE Business, Individual. Bakeries
- Baker's Dozen SEE Settlements. Baker's Dozen
- Ball Act SEE Rent Commission. Ball Act
- Ballet Schools SEE Private Schools. Specific name of school
- Baltimore and Annapolis Railroad SEE Railroads. Washington Baltimore and Annapolis
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad SEE Railroads. Baltimore and Ohio
- Baltimore and Potomac Railroad SEE Railroads. Baltimore and Potomac
- Baltimore and Washington Railway SEE Street railways. Baltimore and Washington
- Bank Examiners, Board of [Missing folder]
- Bankruptcy
- Banks (by date) (includes savings banks and savings and loan associations)
- Banks. Adams National Bank
- Banks. Advance Federal Savings and Loan
- Banks. Amalgamated Bank
- Banks. American Federal Savings and Loan
- Banks. American Indian National Bank
- Banks. American National Bank
- Banks. American Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. American Security and Trust
- Banks. American Trust Co.
- Banks. Anacostia Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Anacostia National Bank
- Banks. Arab American National Bank
- Banks. Bank of America
- Banks. Bank of Brightwood
- Banks. Bank of Columbia
- Banks. Bank of Commerce
- Banks. Bank of Georgetown
- Banks. Bank of the Metropolis
- Banks. Bank of Potomac
- Banks. Bank of Toyko
- Banks. Bank of the United States
- Banks. Bank of Washington
- Banks. Bell and Company
- Banks. Capital Bank
- Banks. Capital City Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Capital One
- Banks. Capital Savings Bank
- Banks. Capital Trust Company
- Banks. Central National Bank
- Banks. Century National Bank
- Banks. Chemical Bank
- Banks. Chevy Chase Federal Savings Bank
- Banks. Chevy Chase Savings Bank (closed 1936)
- Banks. Citicorp Savings
- Banks. Citizens Federal Savings and Loan Association of Georgetown
- Banks. Citizens National Bank
- Banks. City Bank
- Banks. City First Bank
- Banks. Colonial Bank and Trust Company
- Banks. Columbia Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Columbia First Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Columbia National Bank
- Banks. Columbia Realty Trust
- Banks. Commercial National Bank
- Banks. Community Federal Savings and Loan
- Banks. Continental Trust Company
- Banks. Corcoran and Riggs
- Banks. Credit International
- Banks. Crestar
- Banks. D.C. Development Bank
- Banks. Departmental Bank
- Banks. Development Bank of Washington
- Banks. Dime Savings Bank
- Banks. Diplomat National Bank
- Banks. District National Bank
- Banks. District of Columbia National Bank
- Banks. Dominion Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. East Washington Savings Bank
- Banks. Eastern Liberty Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Enterprise Bank
- Banks. Enterprise Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Equitable Investment Trust Inc.
- Banks. Equitable Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Eurobank Inc.
- Banks. Exchange Bank of Washington
- Banks. Export Import Bank of Washington
- Banks. Farmers and Mechanics National Bank
- Banks. Federal American National Bank
- Banks. Federal City National Bank
- Banks. Federal Home Loan Bank Board
- Banks. Financial General Bankshares
- Banks. First American Bank of Washington
- Banks. First Federal Savings and Loan
- Banks. First National Bank of Washington (closed 1873)
- Banks. First National Bank of Washington (opened 1922)
- Banks. First Union
- Banks. First Virginia Banks
- Banks. First Washington Securities Corporation
- Banks. Franklin National Bank
- Banks. Freedman's Savings and Trust Company
- Banks. German American Savings Bank
- Banks. Guardian Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Hamilton Federal Savings Bank
- Banks. Hamilton National Bank
- Banks. Hemisphere National Bank
- Banks. Heritage International Bank
- Banks. Home Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Home Loan and Savings Association
- Banks. Hometown Federal Savings Bank
- Banks. Independence Federal
- Banks. Industrial Bank of Washington
- Banks. International Bank of Washington
- Banks. Jefferson National Bank
- Banks. Jefferson Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. R. W. Latham and Company
- Banks. Latin Investment Corporation
- Banks. Lewis Johnson and Company
- Banks. Liberty National
- Banks. Lincoln National Bank
- Banks. McLachlen Banking Corporation
- Banks. Madison National Bank
- Banks. Mechanics Bank of Georgetown
- Banks. Merchants and Farmers Bank of Anacostia/merchants Bank and Trust Company
- Banks. Metropolis Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Metropolitan Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. MNC Financial
- Banks. Morris Plan Bank of Washington
- Banks. Mount Vernon Savings Bank
- Banks. Munsey Trust Company
- Banks. National Bank of Abu Dhabi
- Banks. National Bank of Commerce
- Banks. National Bank of the Republic of Washington
- Banks. National Bank of Washington
- Banks. National Capital Bank
- Banks. National City Bank of Washington
- Banks. National Consumer Cooperative Bank
- Banks. National Enterprise Bank
- Banks. National Metropolitan Bank
- Banks. National Permanent Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. National Savings and Trust Company
- Banks. NationsBank
- Banks. North Capital Savings Bank
- Banks. Northeast Savings Bank
- Banks. Northwest Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Ohio National Bank of Washington
- Banks. Palmer National Bank
- Banks. Park Savings Bank
- Banks. Perpetual American Bank
- Banks. Perpetual Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Perpetual Savings Bank
- Banks. Petworth Industrial Bank
- Banks. Postal Savings Bank
- Banks. Potomac Federal Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Potomac Savings Bank
- Banks. Providence Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Prudential Bank
- Banks. Public National Bank
- Banks. Regency National Bank
- Banks. Republic National Bank
- Banks. Republic Savings and Loan Association
- Banks. Riggs National Bank
- Banks. Second National Bank
- Banks. Security National Bank
- Banks. Security Savings and Commercial Bank
- Banks. Seventh Street Savings Bank
- Banks. Signet
- Banks. Sovran
- Banks. Standard Savings Bank of Washington, D.C.
- Banks. Tewksbury (Lewis G.) and Company
- Banks. Theodore Roosevelt National Bank
- Banks. Traders National Bank